我和我的哥哥们是历史上
最早的吸血鬼
REBEKAH: My brothers and I
are the first vampires in all of history.
是真祖家族
The Originals.
三百年前，我们帮助建立了纽奥良
Three hundred years ago,
we helped build New Orleans.
现在我们回来，发现这座城市战火纷飞
Now, we've returned
to find a city at war.
吸血鬼马赛尔领导着一支部队
对抗一群绝望的女巫
The vampire Marcel leads an army
against a coven of desperate witches.
我哥哥克劳斯与他们两者为敌
他渴望权力
My brother Klaus is playing against
both sides, hungry for power
希望保护怀着他孩子的狼人
and hoping to protect
the werewolf carrying his child.
但马赛尔有一个优势
But Marcel has an advantage.
他在一个秘密武器的帮助下
俘掳了我们的哥哥以利亚
He holds our brother Elijah captive
with the aid of a secret weapon.
现在为了救回我深爱的哥哥
Now, in order to get back
the brother I love,
我别无选择
只能支援我无法信任的那个哥哥
I have no choice but to side
with the one I cannot trust.
1359年8月
ELlJAH: August 1359.
我注意到兄弟姊妹之间的一个不同
I have noticed a
difference in my siblings.
我们之间的联系
在吸血鬼生活的压力之下更为紧张
Our bond strains beneath the
pressure of our life as vampires.
一旦被吸血鬼的魔性缠身
就会离人性日益渐远
Each day removes them further from
the humanity we once possessed.
我亲爱的妹妹蕾贝卡
变得越来越冷漠无情
My sweet sister Rebekah has grown
quite indifferent to brutality.
然而问题最大的还是我弟弟尼克劳斯
However, the true problem remains,
my brother Niklaus.
他依然用残忍掩饰着自己的孤独
He continues to hide
his loneliness with cruelty.
不过，我依然坚信，我身为他们的大哥
Still, I cling to the hope that I,
as their eldest brother,
可以将他们引上正途
can lead them
down the correct path.
受到家族力量指引的正途
A path charged with the power
of a family united.
如果我失败了
我们的家族只能在黑暗中沦陷
For if I fail, our family's legacy
will end in darkness.
我不敢相信你居然不等我
就自己处理了那些吸血鬼
I cannot believe you disposed
of those vampires without me.
你知道我最爱放火烧东西了
You know how I love
to set things on fire.
难道我该把他们留在前院任其腐烂吗？
Was I supposed to leave them
in the front yard to rot?
再说了，他们是我该负的责任
Besides, they were my responsibility.
他们攻击了怀着我孩子的
无助小孕妇
They attacked the helpless, pregnant girl
who's carrying my child.
你突然对怀着
你混合种孩子的狼人
Oh, I am so moved by your
newfound sense of fatherly duty
流露做父亲的责任感
真让我感动
towards the werewolf carrying
your hybrid bun in her oven.
狼女想知道计划是什么
The werewolf would like
to know what the plan is.
那要看你说的是什么计划，亲爱的
Well, that depends
what plan you mean, love.
是我统治全球的计划
My plan for global domination
还是蕾贝卡在残酷世界中
寻找真爱的计划
or Rebekah's plan to find love
in a cruel, cruel world.
营救以利亚的计划
The plan to rescue Elijah.
你知道，那个好哥哥
You know, the good brother,
被你从背后插入匕首
the one who is now
in the possession
现在落在你死敌手上的那个
of your mortal enemy after
you stabbed him in the back.
明确点说，是从前面
In the front,
if we're being specific.
你们俩说过会救他回来的
You two said that
you would get him back.
那么现在有计划吗？
So is there a plan, or what?
好吧
Okay.
首先，马赛尔不是我的死敌
Well, firstly,
Marcel is not my mortal enemy.
他是我的朋友
虽然他没意识到我正试图破坏
He's my friend, albeit one who is
unaware that I am trying to sabotage
他对整个超自然法语区的控制
his hold over the supernatural
community of the French Quarter,
但尽管如此，还是朋友
but a friend nonetheless.
第二点，我用匕首封住以利亚
是为了赢得马赛尔的信任
And secondly, I daggered Elijah
in order to gain Marcel's trust.
要是我早知道他会把我哥哥
If I had known he would
place my brother
交给一个特别暴躁的小女巫
in the hands of a particularly
nasty teenage witch,
我绝对会考虑做出略为不同的选择
I certainly would have weighed
my options a bit differently.
第三点，妹妹，请说
And thirdly, sister, please.
第三点，正如你所要求的
And thirdly, the plan,
as you have demanded,
计划就是尼克劳斯
直接向马赛尔要回以利亚
is for Niklaus to simply ask
Marcel for Elijah back.
这并不是全部的计划，对吧？
That's not the whole plan, is it?
拜托
Oh, please.
克劳斯作为一个兄弟也许并不称职
Klaus may be a miserable
excuse for a sibling,
但是没有比他更坏心的家伙了
but there is none
more diabolical.
这只是首选计划，亲爱的
That's only the plan "A," love.
但总有备用计划
There's always a plan "B."
备用计划是什么？
And what's plan "B"?
开战
War.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）
剧名：心乱如麻
警方表示目前没有线索…
主演：约瑟夫摩根
MAN (ON TV):
Police say they have no leads...
讨厌，我穿西装太帅了
主演：丹尼尔吉利斯
Damn, I do look good in a suit.
约书亚罗萨，18岁
近日来到…
Joshua Rozza, 18,
had recently arrived....
我在码头的手下会主动站出来
主演：克莱儿荷特
My guy at the docks is gonna
做目击证人
come forward as an eyewitness,
声称他看到这两个喝醉的人
摔进了密西西比河
say he saw those two drunkenly
fall into the Mississippi.
他们会在河里打捞好几周
They'll be dredging for weeks.
没人会到这附近察看
主演：菲比托金
No one will come looking around here.
那很好
考虑到一个死在了…
That's good, considering
one is dead in a dumpster
郡太平间后面的垃圾箱里
主演：查尔斯麦可戴维斯
behind the county morgue and
而另一个现在已经是吸血鬼了
the other one is a vampire now.
主演：丹妮耶拉皮纳达
还有什么吗？
Anything else?
让我来，亲爱的
Allow me, darling.
还有一件事
One thing.
我派了四个夜行者去调查…
I sent four Nightwalkers to look into
法语区出现的一个狼人
主演：莉雅派普斯
a werewolf sighting in the Quarter.
之后就再也没有他们的消息了
I haven't heard from them since.
主演：丹妮儿坎贝尔
(SlGHS)
那上周一共死了十个夜行者了
That makes ten dead Nightwalkers
in the last week.
你觉得是狼人又回到这里
想要制造麻烦吗？
You think the werewolves are back in
town trying to start some trouble?
听着，我知道你和克劳斯是朋友
Look. I know you
and Klaus are friends,
但事实是，自从真祖出现…
but the fact is,
since the Originals showed up--
好了吧，提艾里
你不会还在为之前我给你的
Oh, come now, Thierry.
You're not still upset about that little,
一小口有毒的狼人伤口而生气吧？
toxic werewolf bite
I gave you, are you?
我以为这事已经过去了
I thought we were at bygones.
我看你现在也给了他在你的地盘
自由行动的特权
I see you've given him free reign
of your compound now, too.
没错，就当作是我和我的家人
曾住在这里
Yes. Well, seeing as my family
and I lived here,
事实上是建立了这地方
built the place, in fact.
好了，别这样
你们俩都知道规矩
All right. Come on.
You both know the drill.
提艾里是我的人，亲信
Thierry is my guy, inner circle.
克劳斯是我的老友和父亲
Klaus is my old-time friend and sire.
还是这里的客人
He's also a guest here.
和平共处，行吗？
Peace, all right?
好的
All right.
你有何需要，兄弟？
What you need, my brother?
我想我妹妹蕾贝卡坚持让我要回以利亚
I'm afraid my sister Rebekah is
insisting I demand Elijah's return.
- 她对此非常生气
- 当然
-She's quite worked up about it.
-I'll say.
我们不是要让三个真祖在城里闲晃吧？
We're not gonna have three Originals
walking around town, are we?
我们有一半人都觉得
是他妹妹杀死了夜行者
Half our guys think the sister
killed the Nightwalkers.
那是指控吗？
Is that an accusation?
- 对
- 对一个真祖的指控？
-Yeah.
-Against an Original?
我刚才不是说了要和平共处吗？
What did I say about peace?
来，跟我走走
Come on. Walk with me.
你的亲信缺乏幽默感
制片：兰斯安德森
Your inner circle man
lacks a sense of humor.
他有点过度保护，但十分忠诚
He's a little overprotective,
but loyal to a fault.
在40年代，我救了他
I saved his life
back in the forties,
在退伍军人医院外
发现因战伤奄奄一息的他
found him dying of a war wound
outside a VA hospital.
他会为我杀人，为我而死
He'd kill for me and die for me.
还有，那小子小号真的吹得很棒
Plus, that boy can play the trumpet
like you would not believe.
也许看看今晚能不能让他在派对上…
制片：朗恩麦克劳德
Maybe I'll see if he can play
表演一下
a little tonight at the party.
你会来的，对吧？
You're coming, right?
我怎么能错过认识市议员的机会呢？
How can I miss my chance
to meet the city councilman
他可是接受了你的巨额慈善捐款呢？
as he accepts your gigantic
charitable donation?
他是个蠢蛋
但是为了某些社区服务
He's a schmuck,
but he lets us do our thing
他允许我们做自己的事
in exchange for certain
community services,
比如不把我们的尖牙对准当地人
Iike keeping our fangs
out of the locals.
听着，关于你哥哥
我很想帮你排忧解难
Listen. About your brother,
I would love to help you out,
但提艾里说得对
我的人都紧张不安
but Thierry is right.
My guys are on edge.
他们看到真祖家族回到这里
They see the Original
family moving in,
有吸血鬼死掉，这让他们非常紧张
vampires dying,
it makes them nervous.
如果我现在把以利亚还给你
If I hand Elijah back now,
也许会让他们产生错误印象
编剧：艾胥莉莱尔，巴特尼克森
it might give the wrong impression
搞不清楚这里到底是谁当家
about who's really in charge here.
你懂我的意思吗？
You know what I mean?
导演：克里斯葛端斯莫
你得理解我不得不问
You understand I had to ask.
尼克劳斯，看在老天的份上
Hey, Klaus, for the love
of Mary Magdalene,
一个简单的问题要问多久？
how long does it take
to ask a simple question?
比你想的要久多了
Much longer than you'd think,
因为回答正如预期中一样，不行
considering the answer was,
as expected, no.
马赛尔的手下提艾里很多疑
Marcel's man Thierry is suspicious.
他觉得是你杀死了十个夜行者
He thinks you killed
ten Nightwalkers.
胡扯，我只杀了八个
Well, that's a lie.
I only killed eight.
- 我应该让提艾里成为第九个吗？
- 马赛尔在假装友善
-Should I make Thierry the ninth?
-Marcel is playing friendly.
我们不能杀死他最爱的儿子
否则他会对付我们的
We can't kill the favorite son,
or he'll catch onto us.
- 那就开战吧
- 当然了
-So war it is, then.
-Indeed.
你知道怎么对付那个女巫吗？
Do you know what to do
with the witch?
- 我想我知道
- 很好
-I believe I do.
-Good.
你对付苏菲德弗罗
我来负责下一步
You manage Sophie Deveraux.
I'll take care of the next step.
我命令你放干他的血
I ordered you to drain
him of blood.
怎么这么久？
What's taking so long?
抱歉，我不是什么中世纪拷问专家
Sorry. I'm not, like,
medieval-torture-expert guy.
他到底对你做了什么？
What did he do to you, anyway?
和他做了什么无关
It's not about what he did.
而是我们搞定之后他会做什么
It's about what he's going
to do when we're done here,
也就是我想要他做什么都行
和你一样
which is whatever I want him to,
just like you.
比如，用这个刺穿他的身体
For example,
drive this through his torso.
真是太疯狂了
That is crazy.
我不想这么做，但却做了
I didn't want to do it,
but I did it, anyway.
这叫精神魅惑
It's called mind compulsion.
吸血鬼可以魅惑人类
Vampires can compel humans.
像我和我兄弟姊妹这样的真祖
可以魅惑吸血鬼
Originals, like my siblings and l,
can also compel vampires,
而没人能魅惑真祖
and no one can
compel Originals.
你懂了吗？很好
You following?
Good.
那就是像你这样的全新夜行者
That is how a brand-new Nightwalker
such as yourself
为何在这里在谁都没察觉的情况下
听从我的命令
is here doing my bidding
with no one the wiser.
但我从来没被放干血过
But I never had my guts
drained out of me.
是的，那个嘛，年轻的约书亚
是因为在你体内
Yes. That, young Joshua,
is because I got to you
没有一点马鞭草时
我就已经控制你了
before you had even a drop
of herbal vervain in your system.
马鞭草能阻止魅惑
You see, it prevents compulsion.
马赛尔让他所有的伙伴
Marcel has had his whole
crew taking it
在我回来后开始饮用马鞭草
那也就是为什么
since I returned to town,
and that is why
我们这位朋友需要放干血
our friend here needs
to be bled dry of it
这样我就能魅惑他听从我的命令了
so I can compel him
to follow my every command.
现在我哥哥被俘等待我的营牧
And with my brother currently
in captivity awaiting rescue,
我们就不能那么温柔了
不是吗？
we can't afford to be
gentle about it, can we?
真高兴你能来
Oh, so glad you could make it.
在你磨磨蹭蹭的时候
以利亚身插匕首躺着腐烂呢
Elijah only lies daggered and rotting
whilst you dillydally.
我能来你就该庆幸了
你想干嘛？
You're lucky I came at all.
What do you want?
昨晚海莉被马赛尔的人攻击了
Hayley was attacked
last night by Marcel's crew
因为有人告诉他
在法语区看到一个狼人
because somebody told him
there was a werewolf in the Quarter.
她只去过一个地方
She only made one stop.
在这里看到她的人出卖了她
看好，学着点
Whoever saw her here ratted her out.
Watch and learn.
- 你好，苏菲
- 你好，凯蒂
-Hey, Soph.
-Hey, Katie.
那里面都是金盏花
That's filled with marigold,
很能吸引异性
great for attracting
the opposite sex.
你戴一定很好看
It would look awesome on you.
我十分怀疑
I very seriously doubt that.
你还有其他的吗，比如…
Do you have any others,
one with, say,
我不知道，也许是附子草？
I don't know,
Wolfsbane, perhaps?
附子草？你要那个做什么？
Wolfsbane?
Why would you want that?
别跟我装傻
Please do not play dumb with me.
蕾贝卡
Rebekah!
我只卖了一些药草给那个狼人
仅此而已
I just sold the werewolf some herbs.
That's all.
你在骗我吗，凯蒂？
Are you lying to me, Katie?
我建议你诚实回答我的问题
I suggest you answer
my question honestly.
苏菲
Sophie...
回答她的问题，凯蒂，拜托
Just answer the question, Katie,
please.
是，我告诉别人了，但你不明白
Yes. I told someone,
but you don't understand.
我
I...
我爱他
I love him.
告诉我，你的吸血鬼情人是谁？
Then tell me, who is this
vampire Romeo of yours?
要我数到三吗？
Shall I count to three?
快点
我还要建立一整个部队呢
Be quick about it.
I have an army to build...
一个被魅惑的喽罗可成不了什么气候
(CELL PHONE VlBRATES)
...and one compelled minion
does not an army make.
- 怎么样？
- 叛徒的事你说对了
-Well?
-You were right about the traitor.
幸运的是，她只是个孩子
对我们一无所知
Luckily, she's just a kid
and she doesn't know anything
也不知道我们的目的
about us and what we're up to.
你想听听最能让你高兴的事吗？
Do you wanna hear
what's gonna please you the most?
请说吧
Do tell.
她爱着马赛尔的一个亲信
She's in love with someone
in Marcel's inner circle.
猜精是谁
Guess who it is.
得力助手，钟爱傻帽的那个？
Right-hand-man type,
favors silly caps?
回答正确加两分
Two points for you.
提艾里在和敌人交朋友呢
Thierry is fraternizing
with the enemy.
那就意味着他不知不觉成为了
我们整个计划的关键
That means he just unwittingly became
the key to our entire plan.
我说了这能让你高兴
I told you you'd be pleased.
在一个女巫和吸血鬼对峙的城市里
Oh, to be young and
in love in a city
血气方刚，坠入爱河
where witches and
vampires are at war.
真是太不幸了
How very tragic.
你疯了吗？
SOPHlE: Are you out of your mind?
- 不行
- 这很简单
-No way.
-It's very simple.
我们只要你施一个小小的
非常小的定位咒
We need you to perform
a teeny, tiny locator spell
帮我们找到我们的哥哥
to help us find our brother.
在这个城市使用魔法的女巫都会被抓
Witches who practice
magic in this town
然后会被杀
get caught, and they get killed.
对，关于这点
在我们交易时
Yes. About that,
it seems you left out
你似乎遗漏了一个重要细节
a crucial detail
when we made our deal.
马赛尔的秘密武器
女巫一使用魔法
Marcel's secret weapon,
the way he knows
他就能知道的方法
when a witch is using magic.
这么高的小女孩
很可爱，脾气不大好
Girl about "yay" high,
cute as a button, anger issues.
黛维娜？
Davina?
你在哪看到她的？
Where have you seen her?
不知道
那个小丫头抹去了我的记忆
I don't know.
The little brat erased my memory
就在她用她该死的意念
把我扔出窗外之后
right after she threw me out
a window with her bloody mind.
我来说重点吧
以利亚在黛维娜手上
Let me cut to the chase.
Davina has Elijah.
我想你们女巫
会想把黛维娜和马赛尔分开
You witches, I assume,
want to get Davina away from Marcel.
但我们不知道她在哪
We don't know where she is.
因此，我们需要魔法
Ergo, we need magic.
黛维娜会感觉到的
Davina would sense it.
当然，除非另一个女巫
比如，一个叛徒
Unless, of course, another witch,
say, a traitor to the cause,
比如凯蒂
Katie, for example,
同时在施一个更加强大的魔法
was to perform much more powerful
magic at the same time.
那就制造了一个烟雾弹
That would create a smokescreen
能够掩盖你的小小咒语不被黛维娜发现
concealing your very small spell
from Davina.
凯蒂不该死
Katie doesn't deserve to die.
苏菲德弗罗
Sophie Deveraux....
你不可能这么有原则
You're in no position
to be so principled.
没有战略上的损失是不能赢得战争的
You can't win a war without
a few strategic losses,
不管那损失会有多让人可惜
no matter how regrettable
they may be.
有多少次吸血鬼总是领先一步
How many times have the vampires
been one step ahead,
知道一些他们不该知道的事？
known something they shouldn't?
你的姊姊在大庭广众下被处决
就因为使用魔法
Your sister, executed in the
public square for practicing magic.
谁知道她会被抓？
Who knew she'd be caught?
她有没有试图逃走？
Did she even attempt to flee?
她藏在一艘货船的货舱里
就在船准备在
She was caught hiding
in a cargo hold of a freighter
密西西比河里起航时被抓了
before it set sail
down the Mississippi.
那么，请你告诉我
在马赛尔最重要的亲信中
And who, pray tell,
of Marcel's valued inner circle
谁管理他的码头生意？
manages his business
at the docks?
凯蒂的男朋友提艾里
Katie's boyfriend Thierry.
你说得对，他很不错
You're right.
He's good.
对吧？我叫他音乐人
Right?
"Music Man" I call him.
女士们都爱他，但是他心有所属了
Ladies love him,
but he's spoken for.
他总是和他美丽的小女巫在一起
He knocks around
with this pretty, little witch.
说他爱她，但是我不知道
Says he loves her, but I don't know.
你最重要的战士
在和你的敌人交往
Your brightest soldier
is fraternizing with your enemy,
你却不在意
and you don't care.
我当然在意
但提艾里是个成熟的男人了
Well, of course I care,
but Thierry is a grown man.
他会自己做决定
我也能得到一些重要内情
He makes his own choices,
and I get some good intel.
再说，他也不会做什么
危害我们事业的事
Besides, he's not gonna do anything
to jeopardize what we're doing here.
你瞧瞧
一个吸血鬼主持着一个奢华的慈善晚会
I mean, check this out, a vampire
hosting a ritzy charity event.
我们在这里是一个整体
没人会破坏
We have a community here.
No one is gonna mess that up.
不过呢…
Still....
你还是不会想让那些女巫太大胆妄为
You don't want the
witches to get too bold,
考虑到一个女巫说城里有狼人
given that a witch's tip
about a werewolf in town
导致了你的夜行者的失踪
Ied to the disappearance
of your Nightwalkers.
我确定你考虑过了
I'm sure you've considered
the possibility
这可能是个陷阱的可能性
that it could've been a trap.
也许我该给点暗示了
Maybe I'll send a little message.
提艾里
今晚带一队夜行者去女巫那
Thierry. Take a team of Nightwalkers
to the Cauldron tonight,
小小的骚扰一下
do a little rousting.
提艾里，下手狠一点
Oh, and, Thierry, make it nasty.
所以我就搬回来了
REBEKAH: And so then,
I moved back here
为了更亲近我的哥哥们
因为，说实话吧
to be closer to my brothers
because, let's face it,
家人最重要了，对吧，卡蜜儿？
family is important, right, Camille?
叫我卡蜜，我得改掉这个名牌
Cami.
I have to change this name tag.
喝醉的人都喜欢用法语跟我搭讪
Drunk guys keep hitting
on me in French.
你确定以前没来过这里吗？
你看起来很面熟
You sure you haven't been in here
before? Your face looks so familiar.
你一定是在外头见过我吧
You must have seen me
out and about.
你不是在和马赛尔杰拉德约会吗？
Aren't you dating Marcel Gerard?
他是我的朋友，算是吧
He's a pal of mine.
Sort of.
我听说他喜欢上了卢梭酒吧的金发酒保
I heard he had a crush on the
blonde bartender at Rousseau's.
称不上是约会
他在追求我，算是吧
I would hardly call it dating.
He's wooing me. Sort of.
我不知道
I don't know.
他很有魅力
这大概意味着我该赶快逃走
He's very charming, which probably
means I should run for the hills.
我自己现在有点处在分分合合的状态中
I'm kind of in an on-again,
off-again thing myself at the moment.
那种人最糟了，不是吗？
Those are the worst, aren't they?
那种你摆脱不了的人
就算你很清楚不适合
The ones you can't shake,
even though you know better?
你也一直都非常清楚
And you always know better?
我喜欢你，卡蜜
I like you, Cami.
大部分女孩都很爱发牢骚
Most girls have the unfortunate
tendency of being
嘲讽别人
whiny, little twits.
谢谢你咯
Thanks, I think.
我今晚要去参加那个慈善家举办的
Hey, I'm supposed to go
to this posh charity thing
奢华慈善晚会
thrown by this
philanthropist tonight.
他有点像盖茨比
弄了个很棒的派对
He's a bit of a Gatsby,
throws a mean party.
有兴趣吗？
Any interest?
妹妹
Little sister.
哥哥，我相信我确保了
Well, brother,
I believe I've made certain
马赛尔今晚会有点分心
Marcel will be properly
distracted tonight.
我能问吗？
Dare I ask?
只能说他的注意力不会在我们身上
Let's just say his attention
will not be on us.
我尽了我的绵薄之力
你做了什么来确保以利亚能平安回来？
I did my bit. What are you doing
to ensure Elijah's safe return?
现在呢，为保险起见
我在做些准备以防心软把事情办砸
Currently, I'm preparing insurance
against the tender-hearted.
什么意思？
Meaning?
我们需要为凯蒂找个合适的动机
在今晚施个强大的咒语
We need proper motivation for Katie
to cast a powerful spell tonight.
我在制作动机呢
I'm creating that motivation.
马赛尔下令骚扰女巫
Marcel has ordered
a rousting of the witches.
我就反过来安排事情悲剧地出错
I, in turn, have arranged for things
to go tragically wrong.
明白要怎么做了吗？
You understand what you're to do?
很好
Good.
嘿
Hey.
外面发生什么事了？
What's happening out there?
是克劳斯
Oh, it's Klaus.
他让马赛尔觉得女巫
He's convinced Marcel
that the witches
在计划采取行动对付他
are planning to make
a move against him.
马赛尔想让我们来给个暗示
Marcel wants us to send a message.
不要
Don't!
如果他觉得我有所偏袒
And if he thought
I was playing favorites
就因为我爱上了一个女巫…
because I'm in love with a witch....
再说一遍
Say that again.
我爱你，凯蒂
一切都会没事的
I love you, Katie,
and all this is gonna be okay.
我保证
I promise.
马赛尔也许不在意
提艾里那些你侬我侬
KLAUS: Marcel may not be concerned with
Thierry's romantic entanglements....
那边我已经搞定了
I already got that one.
但还是有些罪过对他而官
没那么容易原谅
But there are other crimes which
he'll be less inclined to forgive.
放开她，滚开
Leave her alone!
Get off!
比如，杀死一个吸血鬼
Killing a vampire, for example.
那就不可原谅了
That would be unforgivable.
如果凯蒂想让她的爱人
免于马赛尔的惩罚
If Katie hopes to save her one true love
from Marcel's punishment...
而想要救他就必须使用魔法
Well, a rescue mission like that will
require something positively magical.
不过话说回来
除了爱情还有什么值得付出生命呢？
But then what's worth dying for
if not love?
（化妆舞会）
? (ROCK MUSlC PLAYS) ?
不得不说，这个布景
很适合今晚的活动
This certainly is a fitting backdrop
for tonight's events, I must say.
她来这里做什么？
What's she doing here?
要让马赛尔分心
还有什么办法比得上
What better way to distract Marcel
than to put his very human,
让他的人类新女友
置身在一个满是吸血鬼的地方呢？
new girl in a room
chock full of vampires?
你好，亲爱的，你好美
Hello, darling.
You look precious.
这个派对真荒诞
但我觉得我会慢慢喜欢上它
This party is ridiculous, and I think
I could pay tuition with this dress.
他就是那个恶名昭彰
令人捉摸不定的家伙？
Is he the infamous
on-again, off-again?
事实上，我是她哥哥
我妹妹说得没错
He's the brother, actually,
and my sister is right.
你的确很美
You do look stunning.
你这身行头也很不错
You clean up pretty well yourself.
别被唬弄了，亲爱的
我可是只披着羊皮的狼
Well, don't be fooled, love.
I'm the devil in disguise.
你们聊吧，我要来点酒
You two chitchat.
I need booze.
- 跳舞吗？
- 好的
-Shall we?
-Okay.
苏格兰威士忌，谢谢
Scotch, please.
你邀请她来是想让自己招人喜欢吗？
You trying to be cute
inviting her here?
我觉得她很迷人
I think she's darling.
我看得出你爱的就是她那颗纯洁的心
I can tell you fancy her pure heart.
或许哪天我会亲手喂给你
Perhaps I'll feed it to you.
你吃醋的样子真好看，蕾贝卡
Jealousy looks good on you, Bekah.
蕾贝卡说的那个人
The guy of hers Rebekah
was talking about.
我觉得应该就是马赛尔
I'm sensing that would be Marcel.
要我就不担心
I wouldn't worry about it.
都是陈年旧事了
Ancient history.
我开始觉得你妹妹是个贱人
I'm beginning to think your
sister is a bit of a bitch.
这个词好像还是她发明的
It's as though she invented the term.
听着
Listen.
抱歉，失陪一下
Pardon me for a moment.
卡蜜
Cami.
派对弄得很不错
Hey, killer party.
这是应付公事的
我本来是要邀请你的…
Oh, it's more of a work thing.
I would've invited you--
没事，不过是约过一次会而已
不需要解释什么
Oh, no. We've been on one date.
No explanation necessary.
你做你的事，我会自己找乐子
You do your thing.
I'll entertain myself.
什么，弃你不顾？
看着你自己玩？
What, leave you alone,
looking the way you do?
想都别想
Hell with that.
你不该到这里来的
You're not supposed to be out here.
你是谁？
Who are you?
抱歉，我不是故意要吓你
我是莎宾，我们见过
Sorry. I didn't mean to scare you.
I'm Sabine. We met.
我是苏菲的朋友
I'm one of Sophie's friends.
你是这里的女巫
You're one of the witches.
苏菲要我在大家
都出去玩的时候过来陪你
Sophie just asked me to come keep
you company while everyone is out.
他是被你吸引来的
You know, it's drawn to you.
你肚里的孩子
一半吸血鬼，一半狼人
The child you're carrying
is part vampire, part werewolf.
你和克劳斯创造了一个很特别的东西
You and Klaus
made something special.
你说话口气像以利亚
You sound like Elijah.
他觉得这个孩子会为我们营造
He thinks this baby
is gonna make us
一个欢乐的大家庭，但他现在却不在了
one big, happy family,
but now he's gone,
还有…
我甚至不知道它究竟…
and I don't even know what...
是什么
...it is.
听着，如果你想的话我可以帮你
You know, I can do something
about that if you want.
我是说，帮你看看是男是女
I mean, find out if
it's a boy or girl.
我还以为你们不能在这里使用巫术
I thought you couldn't do
witchy stuff around here.
这不是巫术，只是一个老把戏
我外婆教我的
It's not magic, just an old trick
my grandmother taught me.
来吧
你一定有点好奇
Come on.
You have to be a little curious.
我记得你说你是做社区工作的
I thought you said you
were in community work.
社区募款
Community fundraising.
办派对，让人们打开钱包捐款
Throw a party,
folks open their wallets.
我就是干这个的
It's kind of my thing.
我大概就是你们说的必要之恶吧
Guess I'm what you call
a necessary evil.
那蕾贝卡呢，她是你的捐款人之一吗？
And Rebekah,
she's one of your donors?
她是个老朋友
She's an old flame.
不可能有多老吧
她看起来比我年轻
Can't be that old.
She looks younger than me.
你会大吃一惊的
我遇见她的时候还是个孩子
You'd be surprised.
I was a kid when I met her.
别再说她了
Enough about her.
我只想跟你在一起
I just want to be
right here with you.
你还真是个令人发指的小恶魔
是不是？
You really are a hideously evil
little thing, aren't you?
胡说，他们两个是绝配
Nonsense.
They're perfect for each other.
你想让马赛尔分心，这不就成了
You wanted Marcel distracted.
Voila.
我该走了
My cue to leave.
失陪
Excuse me.
你到底干了什么？
What the hell did you do?
别在这说，换个地方说
Not here.
No, not here.
我知道你觉得他是个怪物
I know you think he's a monster.
我怎么想不重要
It doesn't matter what I think.
提艾里又杀了一个吸血鬼
Thierry killed another vampire.
他打破了马赛尔最重大的规矩
He broke Marcel's biggest rule.
你再也见不到他了
You'll never see him again.
除非我们做点什么
Unless we do something.
我们？
"We"?
我想救我的族人
I want to save our people.
你想救提艾里吗？
You want to save Thierry?
要达到这两个目的只有一个方法
There's only one way we can do both.
准备好了吗？
You ready?
马赛尔，要出事了
Marcel.
Something is coming.
魔法
Magic.
- 我想听听你怎么说
- 马赛尔，别这样
-I want to hear your side of it.
-Marcel, come on.
你的版本，说
Your version. Go.
我们当时正在扔锅炉
We were tossing the Cauldron.
那个人，某个夜行者
无缘无故袭击了凯蒂
This guy, some Nightwalker,
he attacked Katie for no reason.
他叫麦克斯，是我转变的
His name was Max.
I turned him.
他并不需要什么理由
As far as reasons go,
he doesn't need one.
她是女巫，而他是吸血鬼
She was a witch.
He was a vampire.
现在他死了
Now, he's dead.
我不是有意的
I didn't mean for it to happen.
你打破了我最重要的规矩
You broke my most important rule.
该死，小提
我们做朋友多久了？70年？
Damn it, T. How long we been friends?
Seventy years?
我把你变成了不死之身
I turned you into something
that would never die.
我赐予了你天赋
I gave you a gift.
我对你也一直很忠诚
现在依然是
And I have been loyal to you
all this time, and I still am.
我依然是你的朋友，马赛尔
I'm still your friend, Marcel.
我发誓这没有变
I swear, that hasn't changed.
你是对的，亲爱的
Are you alright, love?
他脾气很大，不是吗？
He's got a temper, doesn't he?
或许现在我该记起我早就知道会这样的
I guess this is the moment
I remember I know better.
这是我们在他女人那里找到的
We found this at his girl's place.
依然是我的朋友，是吗？
Still my friend, huh?
真可笑
That's funny,
因为你的小女巫手里
because it looks to me
like that little witch of yours
有我一直锁起来的咒语
got her hands on a spell
that I keep locked away.
- 马赛尔，我从没见过这个
- 闭嘴
-Marcel, I have never seen that.
-Shut up.
我看你手上依旧戴着
我给你的日光戒指
I see on your hand, you still have
the daylight ring I gave you.
你还要制作戒指的秘方干什么？
So, what would you need with
the recipe for making new ones?
除非你想和凯蒂远走高飞
Unless maybe you and Katie
were gonna go off
自己另立门户？
and start a little kingdom
of your own?
- 不是的，马赛尔
- 让我教教你什么是朋友
-Marcel, no.
-Here's a lesson in friendship.
朋友不会欺骗我，违反我的规矩
Friends don't lie to me,
they don't break my rules,
更不会偷走属于我的东西
and they do not steal what is mine.
监于其谋杀同伴的罪行
For the crime of murdering
one of his own,
我宣判将提艾里范舒囚禁于花园一百年
I sentence Thierry Vanchure
to 100 years in the garden.
好戏上演了
And it begins.
你的决定是正确的
You're doing the right thing.
这是唯一能找到以利亚的方式
It's the only way to find Elijah.
我只是做我该做的
I'm doing what I have to do.
- 凯蒂，不要
- 出现得正是时候
-Katie, no!
-Like clockwork.
快点
Hurry.
不！
No!
你是来救你男人的吧
You're here to save your man.
放马过来吧，小丫头
Well, come on, little girl.
去死吧，你这个混蚤
Die, you son of a bitch.
不要，凯蒂
不要
No! Katie! Don't!
事情不对劲
凯蒂的魔法停止了
SOPHlE: Something is wrong.
Katie's magic stopped.
- 我可以继续
- 不行，她会察觉的
-I can keep going.
-You can't. She'll sense it.
不，我能找到黛维娜
再给我一点时间
No. I can find Davina.
I just need another moment.
你或许可以为了救回你的女巫奋不顾身
You may be willing to die
to get your witch back,
但海莉和孩子会跟着你送死
but Hayley and the baby
will die with you.
以利亚永远不会原谅我们
救回他也会变得毫无意义
Elijah will never forgive us,
and rescuing him will be for nothing.
结束了
我们失败了
It's over.
We failed.
不，凯蒂，不不不
No. Katie.
No, no, no.
不
No.
告诉我
Just tell me this.
她值得吗？
Was she worth it?
我爱她
I loved her.
把他封起来
让他在这腐烂
Seal him up and let him rot.
卡蜜看见了多少？
How much did Cami see?
她只见到了一场争执，兄弟
She just saw an argument, mate.
没什么你应付不来的
It's nothing you can't fix.
你真的很喜欢她，是吗？
You really like her, don't you?
我喜欢她没有被牵扯进这一切的样子
I like that she's not
a part of any of this.
有时用人类的角度看世界
也是一件好事
Sometimes it's good to see the
world the way the humans do.
提艾里的事我很遗憾
I am sorry about Thierry,
you know?
看得出他是你很好的朋友
I can tell he was a good friend.
是我一手打造了他
I made him what he was.
显然我不该信任他
Obviously, my trust was misplaced.
这也不会好过一点
Doesn't make it easier.
你今晚救了我，我欠你份人情
You saved me tonight.
I guess I owe you one.
你想要回你哥哥
You asked for your brother back.
这是我唯一能为你做的了
Seems like the least I can do.
- 卡蜜…
- 想都别想
-Cami--
-Don't even try it.
我知道你为什么来
I get the bro code.
你是来为你朋友说好话的
You're here to smooth things over
for your friend.
你人很好，但…
It's very nice of you, but--
但你曾被伤害过
But you've been hurt before,
你不敢再轻易尝试
and you aren't taking
any more chances.
差不多是这样
Something like that.
今晚我看到的他
不是我想像中的他
The guy I saw tonight?
Not the guy I thought he was.
如果他能这样说变脸就变脸
And if he can turn
on a dime like that....
听起来不止是普通的心碎
Sounds like more than
just a broken heart.
看来有人辜负了你的信任
Someone broke your trust.
卡蜜儿，勇敢的酒保
Camille, the brave bartender.
对不起
I'm sorry.
但我希望你能再给马赛尔一次机会
But I need you to give
Marcel another chance.
看来是我会错意了
Wow.
I totally misread that.
不，你看得很准
但我们都有自己的角色要扮演
No. You read it quite well,
but we all have our roles to play.
你去了马赛尔家，与他共舞
You went to Marcel's.
You danced.
你为他与朋友争执感到难过
You feel badly that he
had a row with his friend,
但除此以外，你只记得
其他一切都很完美
but otherwise, all you remember
is that it was perfect.
今晚真是彻底的失败
Well, tonight was an epic failure.
恰恰相反，妹妹
On the contrary, sister.
今晚成功极了
Tonight was a masterpiece.
你疯了吗？
凯蒂在苏菲完成咒语前死了
Are you mad? Katie died before
Sophie could complete the spell.
我很清楚，是我杀了凯蒂
I'm well aware.
I killed Katie.
你干了什么？
You what?
我们寻死的小女巫一定是
There's no way our
little suicide witch
打算跟马赛尔同归于尽
wasn't gonna try and take out
Marcel with her.
我救了他的命，正因如此
I saved his life,
and in doing so,
他已经在我的控制之中了
I now have him exactly
where I want him.
苏菲信任你
Sophie trusted you.
我信任你，尽管违背直觉
I trusted you against
all my better instincts.
醒醒吧，蕾贝卡
Wake up, Rebekah.
女巫们只为她们自己谋划
The witches are on no one's side
but their own.
她们只想得到那个叫黛维娜的女孩
This girl, Davina,
that's all they want,
当她们拥有了她，你觉得会怎样？
休战吗？
and when they have her, what do
you think happens then, a truce?
当然不是
她们会用黛维娜的力量对付我们所有人
Of course not. They will use
Davina's power against all of us.
即便你说得对，但计划是找到以利亚
Even if you're right,
the plan was to find Elijah,
而你让我们失望了
and you failed us.
你总是对我缺乏信心
You always did lack faith.
由于保护马赛尔，他更信任我了
By protecting Marcel,
I've cemented his trust,
信任到他同意把以利亚还给我们
so much so that he's agreed
to return Elijah to us.
时机一到
等他告诉了我
And when the time is right,
when he has told me everything
黛维娜的所有事
我要亲自掌控她
I need to know about Davina,
I will have her for myself.
我毫不怀疑你能心想事成，尼克
I have all the faith in the world
that you'll get what you want, Nik.
你一向如此
不管我们其他人要付出多少代价
You always do,
no matter what it costs the rest of us.
你让我恶心
You disgust me.
你没事吧？我担心死了
Are you okay?
I was so worried.
谢谢
我感觉到了你所做的一切
Thank you.
Whatever you did, I felt it.
你帮助了我
You helped me.
是那些老家伙，对吧？
It was the old ones, wasn't it?
其实今晚是克劳斯救了我
Actually, Klaus is the one
that saved me tonight.
我要纠正错误
I'm gonna make things right,
首先就是把他哥哥还给他
starting off by giving
him his brother back.
不行
No.
- 什么？黛维娜…
- 不行
-What? Davina--
-No.
你说过那些老家伙很危险
You said the old ones
were dangerous.
在知道怎么杀死他们之前我不会归还他
I won't give him back
until I know how to kill them.
我觉得你可能想知道
以利亚要回来了
I thought you might like to know,
Elijah is returning to us.
恭喜
Congratulations.
我想作恶多端也是有好处的
I guess being diabolical
has its perks.
你不了解他，但你却想念他
You hardly know him,
and yet you miss him.
我的哥哥为何
What is it about my brother
that always inspires
总能引人敬佩？
such instant admiration?
他对我很好
He was kind to me.
有时我会怀疑
我的家族能否得到救赎
ELlJAH:
There are moments when I doubt
my family is capable of redemption.
我今天知道一件事
Hey, I learned something today.
我想是个女孩
I think it's a girl.
但每当我想放弃时
ELlJAH: Yet each time that I am
tempted to surrender,
总会看到一丝善良
支援我坚持我的信念
I see it, the glimmer of goodness
that allows me to believe.
（圣彼得街）
(CHATTER)
你在跟踪我
You're following me.
也许是你挡了我的路
Maybe you're just in my way.
我告诉过你这群邪恶的盟友
是不会带来好结果的
I told you no good would come
from this unholy alliance of yours.
至少我有所作为
At least I'm doing something.
你呢？
What about you?
莎宾，告诉她们你看到了什么
Sabine, tell them what you saw.
是那个狼人女孩
It's the girl, the wolf.
我觉得是个女孩
I think it's a girl.
不，等等
No. Wait.
等什么？
Wait what?
快告诉我这不是个小克劳斯
Please tell me
I'm not having a mini Klaus.
（线上翻译）
（无搜寻结果）
（保加利亚语）
（捷克语）
（无搜寻结果）
（克罗埃西亚语）
（白俄罗斯语）
（无搜寻结果）
（加里西亚语）
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）